module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Who was the first Disney princess created?',
    a: 'Belle',
    b: 'Aurora',
    c: 'Snow White',
    d: 'Cinderella',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What kind of car was the "General Lee" from "The Dukes of Hazzard"?',
    a: 'Dodge Charger',
    b: 'Ford Mustang',
    c: 'Chevrolet Camaro',
    d: 'Dodge Challenger',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following items did Benjamin Franklin invent?',
    a: 'Scissors',
    b: 'Bifocals',
    c: 'Zipper',
    d: 'Printing Press',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many Oscars has Tom Cruise won?',
    a: 'Zero',
    b: 'One',
    c: 'Two',
    d: 'Three',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the medical term for bad breath?',
    a: 'Halitosis',
    b: 'Dyspnea',
    c: 'Epistaxis',
    d: 'Edema',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'A "weevil" is a type of what?',
    a: 'Spellbook',
    b: 'Wrench',
    c: 'Beetle',
    d: 'Sword',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'How much data could fit on a standard 3.5-inch floppy disk?',
    a: '192 MB',
    b: '1.44 MB',
    c: '192 KB',
    d: '1.44 KB',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which beer has the most calories?',
    a: 'Budweiser Select',
    b: 'Bud Light',
    c: 'Beck\'s Premier Light',
    d: 'Michelob Ultra',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What legendary creature creates no reflection in a mirror?',
    a: 'Vampire',
    b: 'Elf',
    c: 'Gargoyle',
    d: 'Leprechaun',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'In George Orwell\'s novel "Animal Farm," what animals control the "government" of the farm?',
    a: 'Cats',
    b: 'Pigs',
    c: 'Goats',
    d: 'Sheep',
    answer: 'b'
  },
];
